## JODIE KWOK



https://www.linkedin.com/in/kwyjodiecs



jodiekwy[at]gmail.com



https://jodiekwy.github.io/ jo-label

Detail-oriented and task-driven software developer with a background in computer science and 6+ years experiences. Development experience with different technologies that are widely used in the industry. Refactored services into automate processed and REST based microservices.

### **SKILLS**

**Programming Languages:** Java, Python, MySQL, PostgreSQL, DynamoDB, HTML, XML, CSS, JavaScript, Angular

**Others:** PyCharm, IntelliJ IDEA, Spring Framework, Django Framework, Kubernetes, Spinnaker, AWS, Terraform

### **EDUCATION**

Stony Brook University Stony Brook, NY Bachelor of Science, Computer Science, December 2016

 Dean's List: Spring 2015 & Fall 2014 & Spring2014 & Fall2013

### **WORK EXPERIENCES**

Senior Software Developer, The Walt Disney Company (Hulu) Oct 2021-Present

- Software Developer
- March 2020-Sep 2021

Los Angeles, CA

- Backend Software Developer on the Ad Platform team; build microservices to support the daily operational needs of the Ad Operation team
- Involved in the invoicing and payment system of the Hulu's Self-Service Advertising Platform—Hulu Ad Manager
- Engaged in the system design for the new Disney Ad Platform with a serverless microservices architecture, including order and campaign management systems
- Focus on integration with multiple internal and external parties and partner with project manager to refine new product requirements

# Java Developer (Consultant), JPMorgan Chase (TEKsystems) May 2019-Feb 2020 Newport, NJ

- Developed REST based microservices to expose different types of banking risk assessment functionalities to Chase customers in a high-volume, high-availability application
- Participated in end-to-end development lifecycle activities of the application, including design, coding, testing and deployment
- Coordinated and collaborated with technical partners for joint application development/testing efforts

# Associate Software Engineer, Fidelity Investment Newport, NJ January 2018-April 2019

- Backend and middle-tier developer on the Fully Paid Lending Program team, a fault-tolerant platform for securities lending market under Fidelity Prime Services
- Managed the messaging system (MQ) for a secure data transmission between different system internally

## IT Administrator, CipherTechs, September 2016-November 2017

New York, NY

 Maintained a smooth operation of the internal network, set up domain policies and deployed software updates to users